And then we'll get, should we be taking questions
or is it just a waste of time?
Because they can ask questions, but,
well, there's Brian, he's good.
But you know what?
In a way, it's a waste of time,
because if you give a great answer,
they don't put it on.
If you give a horrendous answer,
or even if you give a great answer,
they make it sound like it's not a great answer.
They're very dishonest.
Go ahead, Nick.
Yeah, and I think part of that dishonesty
comes from what they see.
For instance, I've never been asked to go
on any other show besides Fox News.
My clips go viral everywhere,
but they've never even asked,
like CNN's never asked, MSNBC's never asked.
And a lot of times when I go to hotels,
I'll stay and I'll watch like MSNBC.
Fortunately, their ratings are terrible.
They are terrible.
MSNBC is dying and CNN is dying like a dog.
And, uh.
Poor CNN, they're so pathetic.
It is very pathetic.
You ever see their anchors in the evening?
Nobody ever heard of them.
When do these people come?
I could take anybody off the street in Washington, DC,
they'd do a better job.
Yeah, and it's not hard to show
what's going on these days.
You literally have an iPhone and you can post it on X.
They don't believe in the star system, you know.
It's just one of those things, right?
Okay, Nick, you finished, Nick?
Yeah, thank you very much.
Are you finished, Nick?
Good job.
Thank you very much.
Well, you've been through hell, I tell you that,
but you're really incredible patriots, incredible people.
Now go ahead, please, Brian.
Brian, go ahead.
I am so thankful for each and every one of you.
Everyone here right now, and I'm very grateful
that my network, Real American Stories,
has partnered up with many of you,
Jack and Sylvia, you have a show on the network,
many of you, Savannah, have appeared on a network as well,
so thank you for being here.
My question is this.
In terms of following the money,
I would just notify that the city of Austin
is cleared to vote tomorrow
to basically waive a $120,000 fee
so that a No Kings, basically an anti-Trump rally
can occur in their city.
They're bypassing the fees, rolling it to the taxpayers.
So my question is to you,
what can the people of Austin, Texas, do right now
to make sure that their tax dollars
don't fund a No Kings, anti-Trump rally coming up?
Well, I think you're astounding.
I would love to do something about that.
Bring a lawsuit, do something.
You know, the best thing you can do is have honest elections
because the elections are totally rigged
in so many of these places.
You know, you take a look.
The people, they're all loving you.
They can't breathe.
They love so much, every one of them.
You don't see one negative.
Then all of a sudden, you lose the election by 20 points.
The elections are so rigged,
and we proved that in 2020 more than any other time.
But even the last election,
there were areas that I won by much more.
We won in a landslide,
but I actually won in more of a landslide than we thought.
I said, you gotta get out, make it too big to rig.
And fortunately, the people made it too big to rig.
They tried, they tried.
But the biggest thing you can do is have honest elections.
You know, if you don't have, and you need great media.
You need great, you need borders.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You need borders.
You need honest media.
You need honest elections, and you have a great country.
And you need all three of them.
Yeah, go ahead.
I was told that Blue Tent had ties
to all these radical groups
that you talked about inside here.
So thank you for removing them.
I would like you to make a big deal, though,
if they're waiving the fee,
but I guarantee they wouldn't waive it if it was a,
if it were a conservative rally,
they wouldn't be waiving it.
So maybe you can look into that, Pam.
Todd?
That sounds like one for Todd, Pam.
Go ahead, Todd.
Good luck.
Mr. President, Mr. President, Mr. President, Mr. President.
Who are you with?
Who are you?
I am with-
What network?
I'm with Al Arabiya.
It's an Arabic network based in Riyadh in Saudi Arabia.
But I am the foreign pooler today.
Mr. President, you said that you might go
to the Middle East on Sunday.
Do you mean Egypt and Israel?
And would you consider going to Gaza
to see what things on the ground?
I might do that.
I may do that.
We haven't decided exactly.
I'll be going to Egypt, most likely.
That's where everybody is gathered right now,
and we appreciate that very much.
But I'll be making the rounds as the expression goes.
I probably will.
Mr. President, Mr. President, Mr. President, Mr. President.
Just to clarify, you said you might go to Gaza.
You're saying on-
Who are you with?
First off, I'm representing the TV pool,
but I'm with NBC, so.
That's too bad.
Okay, well, just to clarify,
you said you might go to Gaza.
And then the second question I had earlier today,
you said the mayor of Chicago
and the governor of Illinois should be jailed.
Have you asked the Justice Department
to look at possible charges?
No, I've seen the law.
And when you have a group of people
where the police call off the safety for ICE officials,
I've understood that, and I've read it today
in numerous journals that that's illegal.
What they did is the, I guess it was ICE, Christy, right?
They were under threat,
and the police were helping beautifully, and it was fine.
And then all of a sudden,
a woman was on the line saying,
everybody, move back, move back, get out, get out.
And they were given an order by the second person
in the police department,
and the governor knew about it, the mayor knew about it.
I understand that's a criminal offense.
Do you wanna comment on that, Christy?
Yes, sir, we're seeing that kind of pattern happen
with local law enforcement and state law enforcement,
not just in Illinois, but also out in Oregon, too.
In fact, in Portland, I was there yesterday,
but some of the ICE officers were telling me
that as they drove by the rioters
that were saying, kill ICE agents,
Molotov cocktails, melt ICE,
that the Portland police were cheering them on
and had their fists in the air cheering on the rioters
that were threatening their lives.
So in Chicago, we had a 10-car caravan
trail our ICE officials and pin them down,
and those ICE officials, to get out of their vehicles,
a woman tried to ram them and run them over,
and shots were fired to get them to safety.
So it's happening on a regular basis,
and any elected official that allows this to happen
and gives cover to those kind of individuals
who are perpetuating murder
should absolutely be prosecuted, in my opinion.
Mr. President.
Daniel. Thank you, Mr. President.
And, by the way, we have Marco Rubio.
Marco, come on up here, please.
He's gonna bring a little stability to this group.
Come on up. Does everybody know Marco Rubio?
Is there anybody that doesn't?
Some of the reporters don't.
They shouldn't be reporters.
Which job is he here for today, sir?
Come on up here, Marco.
Anything we should know about the Middle East?